https://keithtullochwine.com.au/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Keith Tulloch Wine 1907page-template-default,page,page-id-1907,ajax_fade,page_not_loaded,,qode_grid_1300,footer_responsive_adv,qode-content-sidebar-responsive,qode-child-theme-ver-1.0.0,qode-theme-ver-10.1.1,wpb-js-composer js-comp-ver-5.0.1,vc_responsivePrivacy Policy Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy. Keith Tulloch Wine is committed to protecting your privacy.Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfilment of those purposes.We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. DataWhen will we collect data your data?This may include but is not limited to whenYou join our Wine ClubYou purchase wine onlineYou order wine over the phoneYou request wine be freighted to youYou book a wine tasting with usYou book to stay in our Managers Quarters AccommodationYou apply for a jobYou make a Credit ApplicationYou book a function or event with us What type of personal data will we will collect?Information may include but is not limited toIdentification such as name, address, proof of age (over 18years old)Communication details such as email, phoneCredit card details for payment of goods & services Use of DataThe data will be used for the following purposesFor administration & sales of our products & servicesWhere authorised by youWhere we are  required, authorised or permitted by lawTo verify your identityTo comply with laws & regulationsTo provide you with information about products & services from Keith Tulloch Wine that are most relevant to youWe do not sell your details to third parties. Disclosure of DataWe disclose data to Contractors to assist us deliver your order, process payments & communicate with you. These may includeOur freight company for purpose of delivering your goodsOur secure online payment gateway company Data ManagementWe take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal data we hold isAccurateCompleteRelevantUp-to-dateNot misleading Data SecurityWe take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal data we hold is protected from loss, misuse & unauthorised access. In order to prevent any unauthorised access or disclosure of the personal data that we gather, we have in place electronic and managerial procedures to secure and guard this information. Access & Correction of DataYou have the right to access, modify or delete information we hold about you at any time. This is our commitment to take all reasonable steps to ensure that the information we hold about you is accurate, complete and up-to-date. Should you request your personal information be destroyed and cease to be collected, Keith Tulloch Wine will comply with this request.You can access and change your personal information by contacting us here, or if applicable, via the website where you entered your personal information. We encourage you to contact us in order to keep your personal information up to date. Link to other sitesLinks to third-party websites may be provided solely for your information and convenience, or to provide additional information for various other goods and services. If you use these links, you will leave our site. The Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of those websites linked to our site, nor do we control their content or privacy policies. We suggest that you carefully review the privacy policy of each site you visit. Opting out of Marketing & PromotionsIf you wish to cancel your Keith Tulloch Wine Club membership we ask you to make a request in writing & post, or email to us. On receipt we will destroy all your personal and payment information.If you unsubscribe or request we no longer forward you any marketing or mailing list communications we will immediately destroy all your personal information & cease communications. How do I lodge a privacy complaint?If you are concerned that your personal information has been mishandled, or if you wish to obtain additional information about the way we handle privacy issues, you can contact us at:Keith Tulloch Wine989 Hermitage Road, Pokolbin NSW 2320PO Box 20, Cessnock 2325P 02 4998 7500 E info@keithtullochwine.com.auYou can obtain further information about privacy in Australia and the protection of your personal information on the following website – www.privacy.gov.auThis Privacy Statement was last revised on 7th March 2018Liquor License no. LIQW880010353Liquor Act 1982 – It is an offence to sell or supply to or obtain liquor on behalf of a person under the age of 18 years.
